In the 1950s, Los Angeles displaced a
thousand plus Latino families allegedly
to build affordable housing. Instead,
they sold the land to the Dodgers, who
turned it into a monstrous parking lot.
Because, according to parking minimums,
this is what Dodger Stadium needs. Also,
the school your kids go to, the store
you shop at, the apartment you live in,
or the apartment you want to live in but
can't afford because it's too expensive,
because there are too few apartments.
Because we built parking instead of
apartments. Because the apartments that
did get built also included parking,
driving up the cost by tens of thousands
and the rent or mortgage by hundreds a
month. Why? Because of parking minimums.
The end result, 14% of LA County is
parking lots. That's not a joke. The
solution to this madness, reigning in
big parking government and let the free
market decide the cost of parking, which
is currently 99% free in America. And
big government mandated parking
minimums. Let individuals exercise their
personal freedom when deciding how many
lots to have for a building. Build up
those concrete lots with multif family
housing. Bring in some good old mass
transit with tracks and rolling stock
made of American steel put together by
American hands. Smash big government
regulations that keep the free market
down by only allowing single family
homes in an area. Raise your voice
against parking minimums and sign the
petition by Yimi Action today